{
    "id": "f6387456204e45f1b63e36f5a2445fed",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Try not to …………………….. her with such gruesome stories.",
            "description": "Horrify is the verb here.",
            "answers": [
                "horrify",
                "horror",
                "horrible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They are very ………………………. to their guests.",
            "description": "Hospitable means gracious, cordial.",
            "answers": [
                "hostable",
                "hospitable",
                "hospitible"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………… forces fought for possession of the mountain pass.",
            "description": "Hostile is the adjective form.",
            "answers": [
                "hospitable",
                "hostile",
                "hostility"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Helping that family was a very …………………… thing to do.",
            "description": "Both human and humane can be used as an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "human",
                "humane",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "With ………………………. he thanked everyone for their help.",
            "description": "Humility means modesty.",
            "answers": [
                "humanity",
                "humility",
                "humiliation"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to ……………………… him when he is in one of those moods.",
            "description": "Humor can also be a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "humor",
                "humorous",
                "humore"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were asked a ………………………. question.",
            "description": "Hypothetical is the adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "hypothesis",
                "hypothetical",
                "hypothetic"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Not even this bitter experience crushed his ………………………..",
            "description": "Idealism is the belief in noble goals.",
            "answers": [
                "ideal",
                "ideology",
                "idealism"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… can be congenital or caused by some childhood illness.",
            "description": "Idiocy means stupidity. Idiosyncrasy is a peculiar trait or quirk.",
            "answers": [
                "Idiocy",
                "Idiotcy",
                "Idiosyncrasy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Jim is quite knowledgeable but pretends to be an ………………………..",
            "description": "Ignoramus means know-nothing.",
            "answers": [
                "ignorant",
                "ignoramus",
                "ignominous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My departure is ……………………….",
            "description": "Imminent means close at hand.",
            "answers": [
                "imminent",
                "eminent",
                "emminent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Wild animals are ………………………",
            "description": "Amoral means lacking a knowledge of right and wrong.",
            "answers": [
                "immoral",
                "amoral",
                "immortal"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}